To be continued...
If you are not a good one, you will be able to make the sword of the sword.
I will not be able to do this.
This is the first time he won the king's sword.
He's going to the king's sword.
He's not good.
But he's a big sword.
He's going to the king's sword.
Good!
Fire.
Fire!
The king is the king's sword.
Fire.
機具inhox4品上先。 丟人歇允。
哈哈哈,
仙君莫及!
法徒再現!
彼此人 dong短,
It's not a difficult time to kill a lot of people.
It's not like that.
I'm not sure how many people are going to die.
I didn't.
Oh, no, no.
I hated it.
When you got back, you would've had it.
Let's go.
This...
...you know...
...the secret...
Oh, it's so sad...
...the fourth character of the Lord...
...I can't believe that the evil...
...I can't believe that...
...the evil...
...to end the evil...
...and the evil...
...what?
...
Oh, my God.
The second king of the king.
The king of the king.
The king.
Remember your promise.
Let's go.
There are also a lot of people who are now in the old days.
I don't think so.
You are not a good one.
I think so.
It's a lot of people who are now in the middle.
Of course.
Yeah.
This is the end of the day of the day.
It's still the last one.
And that's why it hasn't been a secret.
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
It's the time to fight.
It's time to fight.
You don't have to fight.
Let's go!
看来你的记忆当真已在封印中沉睡太久
那今日连起着朝鲜台让你想起
老夫数百次踏入为仙界 越变古籍 终得慈俭
慈俭所在正是先帝白帆弟子清水仙君的一生
你明清水 乃上古修真国清水国的储君
当年你飞升仙界 便是来到此地朝鲜台
义是在此得与先帝白帆被收为徒
此后数万年 你随白帆征战四方 开奖拓图
容其应子 风光无限啊
可一眼之间 你施了神体 不为魔伤
铸造之人 皆死于你手
你神父极尽神功 最受无人可当 杀命无数
因而 让成为仙界开戒以来 最惨烈之节
直到你师父 先帝白帆清理
你终得清醒 但那错已成
你就走死掉
未来支撞到了 breaks
鹊儿
不 不 不 不 不 gorgeous
不 不ious
varying diverse 暂存
You wake up.
It's me.
I'm back.
Yen.
Don't go!
Notlook.
Elu!
Yen!
Once you say scrap-
雷之中自斬神情,又以法寶封印让自己永不超生。
百凡不倩,在封印外布下瘤伤大阵。
望你万载之后得以松陷。
Your enemy will come back then.
If you wish to make that battle, I would like to ask you for the moment,
no matter what you need.
You will trust me.
Neither of you.
If you kill me,
heal you.
Love you.
Use your word.
Do not need to be done with your entire hunter.
If you like it,
You should be able to move.
I'm not a good one.
That's enough!
What?
You're not a good one.
Is it...
that was when you were killed by the time of the time.
It's not.
Why?
I'll let you go.
Why do you have to believe me?
I'm sorry!
What?
Don't you?
I'm sorry!
You're right.
啊,這才是苦服僵重的威能!
乘水仙君!
你可知,你被封了後不久,你的尸孫百凡便離奇失亡!
雷仙劫易隨之崩塌!
你難道不想...
閉嘴!
換瑜!
Oh my god.
Take a look at the end of the game.
I will be able to reach the end of the game.
If you have a chance,
your life will be able to reach the end of the game.
This reason...
... is too late.
What happened?
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
I've lost my soul.
I am not sure.
I'm not sure.
I have a try.
I have no idea.
I am not sure.
Let's go.
Oh, my God.